<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anjul Sahu</title>
    <link>https://anjuls.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anjul Sahu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All views are personal and I reserve the full rights on content published on this blog.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 18:17:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anjuls.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection on 2019</title>
      <link>https://anjuls.github.io/posts/reflection-on-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 01:32:56 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anjuls.github.io/posts/reflection-on-2019/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new year 2020. I want to take a pause to reflect on the last year on personal and professional front. The year was nearly flat and steady. There were no surprises, spikes like last year especially on the personal side. Personally, I have enjoyed the whole year with the family and friends in Melbourne. 2019 was also a year of change. I changed many projects this year unlike one in past one decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://anjuls.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 21:54:58 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anjuls.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Anjul Sahu (Pronounciation: an.jul saa.hoo, he/his), based out of Indore, India. I am working as Solution Architect and focussed on cloud-native technologies. In past, I have worked as DBA, DevOps engineer, Technical Architect. I also have deep interest in emerging technologies, leadership, entrepreneurship, and programming. In my free time, I do travel and photography.
Please follow me on Twitter and LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://anjuls.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 19:04:42 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anjuls.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hi World! I have setup this blog after various stints which covered personal and Oracle database stuff but for a long time, I have been away from the blogging. The reason is primarily getting busy with family life and switching roles. Last week, I came across my twitter timeline bidding .dev domains and I got excited to reserve my own anjul.dev last night. I intent to call this my permanent home on the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>